# Kushal Mani

I am a highly motivated and results-oriented professional with a diverse background in IT Field. With a passion for Software Development. My journey has equipped me with a unique blend of technical expertise, creative problem-solving, and strong interpersonal skill



kushaldobhal2001@gmail.co m



9999505350



Ghaziabad, India



linkedin.com/in/kushal-mani



github.com/Kushal-M07



medium.com/@kushaldobhal 2001

### SKILLS





### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Antino labs**

# Software Developer Trainee (Frontend)

06/2023 - Present Proiect: Guarented

Guarented is a platform that caters to people who are pro asset free lifestyles or are not keen on spending too much on household products. By providing premium quality goods at budget-friendly prices and excellent customer support services

#### Roles/Responsibilities

- Integration of API's and dynamically sending data
- Performance Optimization: Optimizing API calls and overall Performance
- Worked on the DOM Manipulation
- Worked and Solved the Bugs of the CartPage
- Dynamic Forms Implementations of Different Libraries
- Created reusable components accordingly using Angular Material, Tailwind

# **Getboarded Technology**

### Frontend Intern

11/2022 - 05/2023

Proiect :- VideoWiki

**VideoWiki**: A simple tool for teachers to create teaching content without any advance knowledge of a tool or code. They create by using various media and graphics from the open stock libraries and merging it with their own content to keep it engaging and diverse.

#### Roles/Responsibilities

- Worked on the OpenAl's API integration and generate the real time Solution like ChatGPT
- Worked on the Web3 wallet Integration
- Implementation of Different libraries
- Implementation of Cropper Js
- Re-Built the login/Signup Dashboard From Scratch

### PERSONAL PROJECTS

### CodeSandBox Replica

Created A Code Compiler In which you can select multiple languages and write Code which will be executed and Shows Output and also had the functionality of adding Themes

# **Employee Management**

A dashboard in which I integrated Firebase API for login and signup, added the JSON Local Server for the data manipulation, Created Reusable Components with Code Splitting Techniques

### Learning App

Created a learning App which I named as a Brainiacs where , I upload the Videos on the Firebase Storage Bucket and User Can watch the Video according to the his Needs

# **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor's of Technology Abdul Kalam Technical University

2019 - 2023 74.5 %